Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Mexico File, 1956-1961
  - Correspondence, 1957-1961
    - N-Z
      - Pichardo, Ignacio, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 46)
      - Pietrabissa, Franco, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 64: 47)
      - Pina, Joaquin, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 48)
      - Pina Morales, Maclovio, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 49)
      - Pineda, Antonio, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 50)
      - Pinkham, Charles, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 51)
      - Pinkley, Virgil, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 64: 52)
      - Pino Desandoval, Hylda, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 53)
      - Pistora, Bedrich, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 54)
      - Pitchess, Peter J., 1960 (Box-folder 64: 55)
      - Pitluk, Jack N., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 64: 56)
      - Pitts, L. W., 1958 (Box-folder 64: 57)
      - Plaisted, Harris M., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 58)
      - Plaskett, Wenona de Castro, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 59)
      - Plaza, Galo, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 60)
      - Plenn, Jaime, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 64: 61)
      - Pleuthner, Willard A., 1958 (Box-folder 64: 62)
      - Plowman, L. C., 1957 (Box-folder 64: 63)
      - Plumley, H. Ladd, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 64)
      - Pogue, L. Welch, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 65)
      - Poire Ruelas, Alfonso, 1957 (Box-folder 64: 66)
      - Polivka, J. F., 1957 (Box-folder 64: 67)
      - Polson, Grace L., 1959 (Box-folder 64: 68)
      - Ponce, Bernardo, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 69)
      - Pool, John C., 1957 (Box-folder 64: 70)
      - Portes Gil, Emilio, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 71)
      - Portillo, Bonifacio, Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 64: 72)
      - Posner, Stanley I., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 73)
      - Post, Mary Brinker, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 74)
      - Posz, Paul, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64: 75)
      - Potter, William E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64: 76)
      - Potts, Ramsay D., Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 64: 77)
      - Poulson, Norris, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 64: 78)
      - Pourriere, Berthe, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 79)
      - Powel, N. E., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 64: 80)
      - Powell, Wesley, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 64: 81)
      - Poyo, Ruth, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 64: 82)
      - Poyo-Skillin, Luis, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 83)
      - Pozos, Manuel Alfonso, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 84)
      - Pratt, Tracy, 1957 (Box-folder 64: 85)
      - Premio Real, Jean de, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 86)
      - Prentice, Don M., 1960 (Box-folder 64: 87)
      - Press, William H., 1957 (Box-folder 64: 88)
      - Pressler, Herman P., 1958 (Box-folder 64: 89)
      - Prettyman, Thomas J., 1959 (Box-folder 64: 90)
      - Price, Judy Ann, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 91)
      - Pritchard, Virgil E., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 64: 92)
      - Priest, Ivy Baker, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 93)
      - Prieto, Carlos, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 64: 94)
      - Prieto, Jose Andre, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 95)
      - Prieto, Victores, 1958 (Box-folder 64: 96)
      - Prieto Laurens, Jorge, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 97)
      - Prieto Lopez, Eduardo, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 64: 98)
      - Prieto P., Alejandro, 1960 (Box-folder 64: 99)
      - Prochnow, Herbert V., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 100)
      - Proett, Dwayne L., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 64: 101)
      - Pryor, Samuel F., Jr., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 64: 102)
      - Pugh, Caro MacNeice, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 1)
      - Pugh, Walter D., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 2)
      - Pugh, William C., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 3)
      - Pulido, Jose R., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 4)
      - Pullen, Albert B., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 5)
      - Purvis, Robert, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 6)
      - Pusey, Nathan M., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 7)
      - Putnam, David F., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 8)
      - Putnam, George E., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 9)
      - Pyle, Howard, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 10)
      - Pyle, James T., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 11)
      - Quayle, Oliver A., III, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 12)
      - Quezada, J. Jesus, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 13)
      - Quijano Mendez, Hector, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 14)
      - Quinn, William F., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 15)
      - Quinonez M., Alfonso, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 16)
      - Quinonez S., Ricardo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65: 17)
      - Quint, Bert, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 18)
      - Quintanilla, Luis, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 65: 19)
      - Quirasco, Antonio M., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65: 20)
      - Quiroz, Rosario, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 21)
      - Quiroz Mejia, Efren, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 22)
      - RKO Radio Pictures de Mexico, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 23)
      - Rabasa, Oscar, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 24)
      - Rabb, Maxwell M., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 25)
      - Radford, Arthur W., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 26)
      - Radford School, El Paso, Texas, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 27)
      - Raimondi, Luigi, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 28)
      - Ramirez, Alfonso Francisco, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 29)
      - Ramirez, Gustavo L., 1957 (Box-folder 65: 30)
      - Ramirez, Yolanda, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 31)
      - Ramirez C., Alberto, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 32)
      - Ramirez M., Antonio, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 33)
      - Ramirez Pinto, Arturo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65: 34)
      - Ramirez Torres, Ernesto, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 35)
      - Ramirez Ulloa, Carlos, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 36)
      - Ramos, Carlos, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 37)
      - Ramos Santos, Matias, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 38)
      - Ramsey, Ben, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 39)
      - Ramsey, Henry C., 1957 (Box-folder 65: 40)
      - Ramspeck, Robert, 1957 (Box-folder 65: 41)
      - Ranck, E. W., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 42)
      - Rand, John A., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 43)
      - Randall, Clarence B., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 44)
      - Ransom, Charles G., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 45)
      - Ransom, Floyd D., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 46)
      - Ransom, Harry H., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 47)
      - Rash, James R., Jr., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 48)
      - Rastetter, Richard W., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 49)
      - Rathbun, Lawrence W., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 50)
      - Rather, Mary, 1957 (Box-folder 65: 51)
      - Rau, Inge, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 52)
      - Rau, Ottmar H., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 53)
      - Ravotto, J. D., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 54)
      - Ray, Maggie, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 55)
      - Ray, Philip Alexander, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 65: 56)
      - Reagan, James R., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65: 57)
      - Rebello, Madeline, 1957 (Box-folder 65: 58)
      - Reber, Lindsey, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 59)
      - Rebolledo, Lucino M., 1958 (Box-folder 65: 60)
      - Reddick, DeWitt C., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 61)
      - Redo, Diego, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 62)
      - Redo, Joaquin, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 63)
      - Reed, M. Clarke, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 64)
      - Reed, Paul K., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 65)
      - Reed, William L., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 66)
      - Reedy, Margaret M., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 65: 67)
      - Regalado, Tomas, Jr., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 65: 68)
      - Reid, Bert, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 69)
      - Reilly, Judith, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 70)
      - Reiser, Ben A., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 71)
      - Reist, Jay, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 72)
      - Republica Sindical, undated (Box-folder 65: 73)
      - Republican Party. National Committee, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 65: 74)
      - Reston, James, 1957 (Box-folder 65: 75)
      - Retolaza de Sanchez, Dolores, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 76)
      - Reuther, Walter, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 77)
      - Rey Perna, Santiago, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65: 78)
      - Reyes, Humberto V., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 79)
      - Reyes, Manuela M. de, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 80)
      - Reynolds, Milton, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 81)
      - Rhodes, Robert W., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 82)
      - Rhuberry, Fraine B., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 83)
      - Ribeiro da Silva, Manuel Pedro, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 84)
      - Rice, R. J., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 85)
      - Rice, Tolbert A., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 86)
      - Richards, Arthur L., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 87)
      - Richards, Dexter, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 65: 88)
      - Richards, J. Dudley, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 89)
      - Richards, John R., 1960 (Box-folder 65: 90)
      - Richardson, William B., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 65: 91)
      - Richmond, Elsie, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 92)
      - Rickenbacker, Edward V., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 65: 93)
      - Riddle, Olive, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 94)
      - Riddleberger, James W., 1959 (Box-folder 65: 95)
      - Rihani, Jose, 1959 (Box-folder 65: 96)
      - Riley, Jack, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 97)
      - Riley, Phelps T., 1957 (Box-folder 65: 98)
      - Riley, W. Douglas, Jr., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 65: 99)
      - Rines, Joseph, 1960 (Box-folder 65: 100)
      - Riso, Ovid, 1958 (Box-folder 65: 101)
      - Ritter, Irving, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 1)
      - Ritter, James G., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 2)
      - Riva Palacio, Manuel, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 3)
      - Rivadeneyra Falco, Luis G., 1958 (Box-folder 66: 4)
      - Rivas R., Antonio, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 5)
      - Rivas Vallejo, Adolfo, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 6)
      - Rivera, Andres, Jr., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 66: 7)
      - Rivera, Hector, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 8)
      - Rivera, John A., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 9)
      - Rivera, Larry, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 10)
      - Rivera Garcia, Lucio, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 11)
      - Rivero Quijano, Jesus, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 66: 12)
      - Roach, Richard E., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 13)
      - Roberts, Wilbur H., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 14)
      - Robertson, Bruce, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 15)
      - Robertson, Rhodes, undated (Box-folder 66: 16)
      - Robertson, Walter S., 1957 (Box-folder 66: 17)
      - Robinson, Elwood J., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 18)
      - Robinson, Hamilton, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 19)
      - Robinson, Harold R., 1958 (Box-folder 66: 20)
      - Robinson, T. A., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 21)
      - Robinson, William E., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 22)
      - Robles Gil, Javier, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 23)
      - Robles Ramos, Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 24)
      - Roca, Miguel Angel, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 25)
      - Roche, Mary M., 1957 (Box-folder 66: 26)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 27)
      - Roderick, George H., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 66: 28)
      - Rodriguez, Abelardo L., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 29)
      - Rodriguez Adame, Julian, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66: 30)
      - Rodriguez Anciola, Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 31)
      - Rodriguez Macedo, Adrian, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 32)
      - Rodriguez Perez, Luis, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 33)
      - Rodriguez Sarabia, Luis, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 34)
      - Roettinger, Phil C., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 35)
      - Rogel, Max, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 36)
      - Rogers, Charles F., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 66: 37)
      - Rogers, Clyde L., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 38)
      - Rogers, Donald I., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 39)
      - Rogers, Donald W., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 40)
      - Rogers, Timothy J., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 41)
      - Rogers, Vance, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 42)
      - Rogers, W. J., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 43)
      - Rohe, Bernhard, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 44)
      - Roig, Harold J., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 66: 45)
      - Rojas Mejia, Miguel A., 1957 (Box-folder 66: 46)
      - Roll, Sylvester J., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 66: 47)
      - Rolland, Alberto J., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 66: 48)
      - Rolland, Modesto C., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 49)
      - Romero, Pepe, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 66: 50)
      - Romero C., Guillermo, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 51)
      - Romero de Valle, Emilia, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 52)
      - Romero Lopetegui, Mario, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 53)
      - Romero Palafox, Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 54)
      - Romero Perez, Humberto, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 55)
      - Romualdi, Serafino, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 56)
      - Romulo, Carlos P., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 57)
      - Roofe, Glenn O., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 58)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 59)
      - Roosevelt, Selwa, 1957 (Box-folder 66: 60)
      - Roper, J. Clinton, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 61)
      - Rosado Espinola, Raul, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 62)
      - Rosen, Ronald E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66: 63)
      - Rosenbaum, Joseph H., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 64)
      - Rosenberry, Walter S., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 65)
      - Rosenhouse, Harvey, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 66)
      - Ross, Carl D., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66: 67)
      - Ross, Carol E., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 68)
      - Ross, Frank A., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 69)
      - Ross, James S., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 70)
      - Ross, Mrs. Warren B., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 71)
      - Rosset, Barney, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 72)
      - Roth, Charles David, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 66: 73)
      - Roulston, William T., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 74)
      - Rovzar, Alexis E., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 75)
      - Rowles, E. W., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 76)
      - Roy, Leo M., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 66: 77)
      - Roy, Lionel V. J., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 78)
      - Royal Society of St. George, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 79)
      - Ruane, William J., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 80)
      - Rubalcaba, Filiberto, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66: 81)
      - Rubi Olivera, Gilberto, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 82)
      - Rubin, A., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 83)
      - Ruff, Roberto M., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 66: 84)
      - Ruffin, H. D., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 85)
      - Ruiz Camarillo, Eladio C., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 86)
      - Ruiz Cortines, Adolfo, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 66: 87)
      - Ruiz Galindo, Antonio, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 66: 88)
      - Rule, Gordon W., 1957 (Box-folder 66: 89)
      - Rummell, Robert M., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 90)
      - Ruppel, A. J., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 66: 91)
      - Rupple, George, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 92)
      - Rush, Clive H., 1958 (Box-folder 66: 93)
      - Rushing, E. O., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 94)
      - Rusk, Howard A., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 66: 95)
      - Russell, Charles H., 1958 (Box-folder 66: 96)
      - Russell, Gerald W., 1958 (Box-folder 66: 97)
      - Russin, Robert I., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 98)
      - Rutter, Homer R., 1959 (Box-folder 66: 99)
      - Rutter, Lynn, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 100)
      - Saenz de Miera, Antonio, 1958 (Box-folder 66: 101)
      - Saenz Royo, Artemisa, 1959 (Box-folder 66: 102)
      - Sahlou, Petros, 1960 (Box-folder 66: 103)
      - Saizar, Martin M., 1960 (Box-folder 66: 104)
      - Salas, E. Guillermo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 1)
      - Salas Portugal, Armando, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 2)
      - Salcedo Ledesma, Enrique, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 3)
      - Salinas, Ezequiel D., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 4)
      - Salinas Carranza, Alberto, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 5)
      - Salinas Leal, Bonifacio, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 6)
      - Salinas Lozano, Raul, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 7)
      - Salinas Ramos, Alberto, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 67: 8)
      - Salvat, Agustin, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 9)
      - Sanchez, Enrique Fernando, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 10)
      - Sanchez, Maria Ofelia, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 67: 11)
      - Sanchez Calderon, Oscar, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 12)
      - Sanchez Fogarty, Federico, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 13)
      - Sanchez Garcia, Luciano, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 14)
      - Sanchez Gavito, Vicente, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 15)
      - Sanchez Martinez, Lucino, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 16)
      - Sanchez Mireles, Romulo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 17)
      - Sanchez Mora, Ignacio, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 18)
      - Sanchez Navarro, Juan, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 19)
      - Sanchez Orrego, Alberto, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 20)
      - Sandlin, Marlin E., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 21)
      - Sandoval, Marcela, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 22)
      - Sandoval Vallarta, Manuel, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 23)
      - Sandoval Vallarte, Mrs. Manuel, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 24)
      - Sandvig, Mauda, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 25)
      - Santarelli C., Leonardo, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 67: 26)
      - Santoscoy, Julio, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 27)
      - Sanville, Dave, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 28)
      - Saucedilla, Condesa de, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 29)
      - Sauer, Carl A., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 30)
      - Savin Romero, Adolfo, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 31)
      - Scanlan, F. T., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 32)
      - Scantlebury, Ronald E., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 33)
      - Schaefer, Carl, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 34)
      - Schaefer, George M., 1958 (Box-folder 67: 35)
      - Schaeffer, William Lawrence, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 67: 36)
      - Scharf, Manuel L., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 37)
      - Schmidt, G. Lewis, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 38)
      - Schneider, Stephen E., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 39)
      - Schriver, Richard J., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 40)
      - Scott, John R., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 41)
      - Sedillo, Sonia M., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 42)
      - Seffel, G. W., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 43)
      - Sendel, Federico, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 44)
      - Sevier, John H., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 45)
      - Sevier, Randolph, 1957 (Box-folder 67: 46)
      - Sevilla Sacasa, Guillermo, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 47)
      - Seward, William R., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 48)
      - Shackelford, F. L., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 49)
      - Shaltiel, David, 1957 (Box-folder 67: 50)
      - Shanks, Carrol M., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 51)
      - Sharp, Dudley C., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 52)
      - Shaw, B. T., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 53)
      - Shedd, Margaret, 1957 (Box-folder 67: 54)
      - Shelburne Studios, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 55)
      - Sheley, Horace W., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 56)
      - Shepherd, Lemuel C., Jr., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 57)
      - Sherrod, Robert, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 58)
      - Shields, Robert H., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 67: 59)
      - Shivers, Allan, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 60)
      - Shneerson, Mordekhai, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 61)
      - Short, Laurie, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 62)
      - Shoup, David M., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 63)
      - Shoup, Merrill E., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 64)
      - Shute, Henry A., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 65)
      - Shuttleworth, Herbert L., II, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 66)
      - Siciliano, Rocco C., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 67)
      - Siegars, Russell L., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 68)
      - Sierra, Adolfo, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 69)
      - Sierra, Justo, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 67: 70)
      - Sierra Dominguez, Sergio, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 67: 71)
      - Silva, Jesus R., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 72)
      - Silva, Jorge de, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 73)
      - Silva L., Manuel, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 67: 74)
      - Silver, El., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 75)
      - Silverberg, Abe, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 76)
      - Silverman, Louis L., 1957 (Box-folder 67: 77)
      - Sim, J. M., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 78)
      - Simpson, Mary, 1957 (Box-folder 67: 79)
      - Sims, Harold, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 80)
      - Singmaster, E. H., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 81)
      - Sipes, Alice H., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 82)
      - Sisk, H. R., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 83)
      - Slay, Edgar L., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 84)
      - Slaymaker, Gene A., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 85)
      - Slick, Tom, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 86)
      - Slotkin, Stanley S., 1958 (Box-folder 67: 87)
      - Smith, C. Alphonso, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 88)
      - Smith, C. R., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 89)
      - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 90)
      - Smith, Clement A., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 91)
      - Smith, David, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 92)
      - Smith, Earl E. T., 1957 (Box-folder 67: 93)
      - Smith, Frank, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 94)
      - Smith, H. Gerald, 1961 (Box-folder 67: 95)
      - Smith, H. Hilman, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 96)
      - Smith, Jay Reynolds, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 97)
      - Smith, Lester A., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 98)
      - Smith, Marion R., 1959 (Box-folder 67: 99)
      - Smith, Robert, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 100)
      - Smith, Roderick A., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 101)
      - Smith, Walter Bedell, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 102)
      - Smitmanns Lopez, Juan, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 103)
      - Smoot, Charles Effinger, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 104)
      - Snellgrove, Frank, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 105)
      - Snyder, E. Russell, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 106)
      - Snyder, John W., 1958 (Box-folder 67: 107)
      - Sohm, Earl D., 1958 (Box-folder 67: 108)
      - Soldatic, Dalibor, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 67: 109)
      - Solis Anduze, Fernando, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 67: 110)
      - Solis Martinez, Salvador, 1958 (Box-folder 67: 111)
      - Sollenberger, Howard E., 1957 (Box-folder 67: 112)
      - Sollenberger, W. S., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 113)
      - Solorzano, Gonzalo, 1957 (Box-folder 67: 114)
      - Solorzano, Jesus, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 115)
      - Solorzano Forbes, Salvador, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 116)
      - Sommer, Charles G., 1958 (Box-folder 67: 117)
      - Sotelo Aleman, J. Jesus, 1959 (Box-folder 67: 118)
      - Soto Peimbert, Emilio, 1960 (Box-folder 67: 119)
      - Sours, Lawrence P., 1960 (Box-folder 67: 120)
      - Spangler, Janet, 1958 (Box-folder 68: 1)
      - Speakes, John, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 2)
      - Spector, M. L., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 3)
      - Spencer, Mrs. Lewis, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 4)
      - Stagg, Hazel G., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 5)
      - Stahlman, James G., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 6)
      - Stanford Research Institute, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 7)
      - Stanton, Frank, 1959 (Box-folder 68: 8)
      - Stanton, W. H., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 9)
      - Stark, Robert L., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 10)
      - Stass, Joseph S., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 11)
      - Steadman, Charles W., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 68: 12)
      - Steele, Harry, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 13)
      - Steffensen, Winifred M., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 14)
      - Stein, Lawrence M., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 15)
      - Stevens, Stanford, 1959 (Box-folder 68: 16)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 68: 17)
      - Stieg, Henry P., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 68: 18)
      - Stillwell, James A., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 19)
      - Stinyard, Ellsworth L., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 20)
      - Stirling, Cedric W., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 21)
      - Stockdale, Mrs. Percival L., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 22)
      - Stone, Donald C., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 23)
      - Storey, Edward J., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 24)
      - Stratton, Samuel S., 1961 (Box-folder 68: 25)
      - Street, John Milton, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 26)
      - Stringer, McNeil S., Jr., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 27)
      - Strom, Carl W., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 28)
      - Stroman, James H., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 29)
      - Stunzi, Jacques R., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 30)
      - Stupp, Erwin P., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 31)
      - Suarez, Eduardo, 1958 (Box-folder 68: 32)
      - Suarez, Edward W., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 33)
      - Suarez, Luis M., 1957 (Box-folder 68: 34)
      - Suarez, Mariano R., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 35)
      - Suarez de Cisneros, Luz Maria, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 36)
      - Suarez Rivas, Jose, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 68: 37)
      - Sullivan, Ann A., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 38)
      - Summerfield, Arthur E., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 68: 39)
      - Susman, Ralph W., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 40)
      - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1958 (Box-folder 68: 41)
      - Sweet, Gordon W., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 42)
      - Swift, Erby E., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 43)
      - Swing, Joseph M., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 44)
      - Tafel, Victor, 1959 (Box-folder 68: 45)
      - Taft School, Watertown, Conn., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 68: 46)
      - Taggart, Curtis L., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 47)
      - Tagle Balbas, Francisco, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 48)
      - Taillon, W. L., 1960 (Box-folder 68: 49)
      - Tainter, Judith, 1959 (Box-folder 68: 50)
      - Talbott, Philip M., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 68: 51)
      - Talcott, E. M., 1958 (Box-folder 68: 52)
      - Taliaferro, J. C., 1957 (Box-folder 68: 53)
      - Tallamy, B. D., 1959 (Box-folder 68: 54)
      - Talley, Clarence, 1957 (Box-folder 68: 55)
      - Tamayo Perez, Ruben, 1960 (Box-folder 68: 56)
      - Tane Company, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 68: 57)
      - Tapia Freyding, Jose Maria, 1958 (Box-folder 68: 58)
      - Tardiff, Guillermo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 68: 59)
      - Tatspaugh, Edna H., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 68: 60)
      - Tattersfield, J. Peyton, 1958 (Box-folder 68: 61)